Let's finalize the contract.
συμβόλαιο
With this, the contract is finalized.
Yes.
I will do the rest at my own discretion.
Please do.
Your daughter is safe with me.
It seems you aren't named
the Glutton for nothing.
I suppose.
I'll take that brain.
Oh, gross.
So who is this anyway?
Probably an assassin from
an opposing sub-faction.
So not even Eugenics is a monolith.
Yes. Our own organization is quite
convoluted in that respect.
Therefore, I must acquire that
vessel as soon as possible,
so that I may reach even greater heights.
Vessel, huh?
Is it really that girl though?
It is.
I am absolutely certain.
The Magic Chevalier just
confirmed it for me.
She is definitely the vessel.
Well, as long as I can earn money
and feed, it is all the same to me.
The time for our revenge is finally upon us.
Yes, and I only need Rebecca Bradley for it.
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 10
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Sets Up a Maid Cafe
Good morning, Miss Rebecca.
Ray.
Good morning.
So you've... heard. Haven't you?
I have. Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'll still be coming to the
academy until I graduate.
I'm glad to hear that.
The academy wouldn't be
the same without you.
I'm happy.
Miss Rebecca?
It's nothing.
Once again, I look forward
to working with you.
Likewise!
What do you think?
Can you do it?
If we start from scratch it'll
be hard to get them all done in time...
But maybe if we start with off-the-shelf items...
Then you can do it!
It would be hard to do it all by myself,
but I think we could
it if other people helped.
That's wonderful, Elisa!
You're going to wear it, too, right?
Wha? Me, too?
Obviously!
Take a good look!
There's no world where it would be okay for
you to not wear something this cute.
But... But...
B-B-B-But wait a minute!
But this outfit shows quite a bit of leg,
and the chest area is more
than a little bit prominent!
I-It's too embarrassing!
You'll be fine. I'm going to wear it, too!
That doesn't help me!
Elisa, I can't wait.
Ray, Amelia's being weird!
Do something.
Elisa, I am also interested
in your lovely form.
You are far more beautiful
and cute than you know.
I will vouch for that.
So please, won't you wear it, too?
Elisa...
Won't you?
F-Fine!
If you insist like that!
I'll do it.
Thank you, Elisa!
Rose Kick!
Amelia, that hurt.
Whatever!
I mean, I already knew.
I already knew, but still!
Put that a little more to the right.
Rotate fifteen degrees.
No! Counter-clockwise!
White!
What do you think so far?
It's better than I ever imagined.
I can't believe you've made
this much progress already.
Everybody's super motivated!
Really?
Yeah!
Lads, let's make this one a success, eh?!
Let's go!
Let's do it!
Your words,
We've got this!
your passion,
it all resonated in our hearts.
Albert?
It's true.
When I first got here, I would have
never imagined a scene like this.
Everyone...
So how's... that angle coming along?
It's perfect.
Elisa agreed, too.
Really?!
Oh, yeah!
Even the shy Elisa?!
Come on lads, let's do this!
What's happening?
Once again, your actions
have united everyone.
Ray.
It means there isn't a man on this
earth who doesn't like maid outfits.
A maid cafe?
Yes.
Well, I don't think there's a
problem with the idea itself,
but I'm surprised all the
noble students agreed to it.
Miss Sera.
There isn't a person on this earth
who doesn't like maid outfits.
What?
Fine, whatever.
The paperwork is all in order,
so consider it filed.
You can go back now.
May I ask you a question?
Yes?
Where is the rest of the student council?
I don't know if you're just
too eagle-eyed or what...
Miss Rebecca?
I think we could tell Ray...
The other members are no longer coming.
Why would they not?
It's because of my engagement.
And why would that be?
The secretary of the
student council, Cornea...
Apparently, she was originally slated
to be engaged to Lord Evan.
Lord Evan?
Evan Bernstein.
He is my fiancé.
So what that means is that
I've stolen Cornea's fiancé.
The others have aligned with her
and are boycotting the meetings.
Which is why now Dina and I are the only
ones left to do the student council work.
So that's what happened.
I understand.
Please allow me to help!
I figured you would say that.
But don't you have your own
class's event to help with?
Ever since I've come to this academy,
both of you have been immensely helpful to me.
Not just with the gardening club
and the Magic Chevalier...
so please let me repay
that favor now.
I want to help you two, any way that I can!
Ray...
Jeez, Ray.
Then, let's accept his help, Rebecca.
With him on board, I'm sure we can...
Miss Rebecca.
All right.
Ray, we will count on you, then.
Of course!
Ray, do you have a moment?
Yes, what is it?
I have a favor to ask of you.
Sure.
You should ask what it is first.
There is nothing you could ask
of me that I would refuse.
There you go again.
I think there's something going
on with Rebecca's engagement.
What do you mean?
Nobody heard even a whisper
about this before,
and then suddenly it happened.
Not to mention, House Bradley is
one of the top three noble houses.
If you pause to think about it,
this is completely unthinkable.
I see.
There must be something to Evan Bernstein.
Miss Rebecca won't tell me anything, though.
I'm sure she's trying to protect me
from getting mixed up in something.
Which is exactly why I can't get
any closer to her on this topic.
But I'm sure you could.
Please.
Stay close to Miss Rebecca.
Certainly.
You can count on me.
Thank you, Ray.
Master, I apologize for such a late visit.
It's fine.
But you don't often show up out of the blue.
Did something happen?
Yes.
About the House Bradley engagement...
Evan Bernstein...
Do you know anything, Carla?
House Bernstein is a family
in the upper echelons.
Their standing and sorcery prowess
leaves nothing to be desired,
even for the top three houses.
I see.
So there's nothing strange about
Miss Rebecca's engagement here.
Still, considering Rebecca's age,
this engagement does seem rushed.
It's natural to think that.
Carla, would you mind?
I'll need about a week.
Then, please.
Understood.
Please do.
By the way Ray, what are you
doing for the cultural festival?
We're doing a maid cafe.
A maid cafe?
So, a cafe with maids?
What is that good for?
Master, there isn't a life form on this
earth that doesn't like maid outfits.
Hmm.
So that means you like them, as well?
Yes.
I like Miss Carla's maid outfit, too.
What?!
Master Ray, please.
Actually, when Amelia first approached
me with the idea of the maid cafe,
the very first thing that came to mind
was a beautiful vision of Miss Carla.
Ray, oh you...
I realized there's something
tangibly attractive to maid outfits...
that grabs your heart.
You mustn't...
Ray! Don't rush to conclusions!
That's just deception!
If I were to put on a maid outfit,
wouldn't the effects be amazing?
Welcome home!
You, in a maid outfit, Master?
That's a good joke!
A gorilla can't be a maid!
Huh? You want to die?
My deepest apologies for the disrespect.
It's settled.
Carla and I will be there for
the cultural festival, as well.
Looking forward to it.
Wonderful!
I am overjoyed and grateful!
That dream again.
Why is Ray...
Why?
Hello?
Maria!
What are you doing here at this hour?
I got sweaty, so I took a shower.
Isn't that blood?
Um, I got a little nosebleed.
Maybe I got too hot.
That's unusual for you.
It's late.
You should to go to bed, too.
Are you all right?
With the engagement...?
It's fine.
I am the eldest daughter of one
of the three great houses.
I hope you'll actually have love.
Hey, wait!
Look at that kid.
They're so creepy.
Like, all white.
So weird!
Right?
Big sister, am I weird?
Not at all!
You're very cute.
Really?
That's right!
Your white skin and hair.
And then, your red eyes.
You're very pretty.
It doesn't matter what anyone says.
I think you're very adorable.
Maria, what have you done to yourself?!
That is not how a daughter of one of
the three great houses should look!
Take a leaf out of Rebecca's book!
My sister is so wonderful.
So elegant and pretty.
Your pride and joy who you
can show around anywhere,
with good grades to boot.
Just leave me alone and let me be a failure!
Maria!
Why do I have to look like this?
Why do I not have any talent?
Why can I not be like my sister?
I heard it from Father.
What is the story behind this engagement?
I knew something was going on!
It's none of your business.
Why are you hiding it?
You wouldn't be looking so sad if
it was an ordinary engagement!
Go home.
Now that's something.
I can really feel the
cultural festival vibe now!
Yeah, I'm excited.
You look wonderful, Wanda!
R-Really?
I was skeptical, at first, but not anymore.
Maid outfits are so great.
Indeed.
You all look beautiful.
White?
Those dresses really suit you.
Oh, come on.
You're exaggerating!
Jeez.
Ray.
What do you think?
Wow!
Wow, it's spectacular!
Beautiful!
The maid outfit accentuates
your beauty even more.
Gorgeous!
Well, thanks!
Oh, and don't you think Elisa
looks really cute, too?
I-Is this all right?
Elisa, it's splendid!
Even better than I could have ever imagined.
It looks very cute.
Th-Thank you.
I guess it's good that I put it on.
It really is.
Rose Punch!
Amelia, that hurts.
I mean, I already knew!
I already knew, but still!
Damn you, Ray!
And the thing with the student council!
You realized?
Of course I did.
As if you could leave Rebecca hanging.
You got me there.
Well, that's what's good about you,
so it can't be helped, but...
It can't be helped, but...
Rose Magnum!
Amelia, that hurts.
Shut up!
So cute.
Claris?
I'm jealous of your maid cafe.
What's with the outfit?
Our class is doing a haunted mansion.
It looks cute!
It's supposed to be what some foreign
country's ghosts look like.
It does suit you quite well. Very cute.
I'm not sure how I feel
about being called cute
when I'm supposed to be a
ghost, but I'll take it.
Thanks.
Claris, I love your foreign costume!
Amelia, come on!
Exotic is the best!
This is already pretty high level.
But we can push it one step further.
And the three hairs are cute, too!
Amelia, stop!
So how's Ray's class doing?
It's got a very nice feeling.
They're quite united,
with Ray at the center of it all.
I see.
Yup!
I see...
Ray?
I'll walk you home.
So you're no longer using the dorms?
Yes.
I am engaged, after all.
I think I'll be moving out of the dorms
once the cultural festival is over.
I see.
The cultural festival is almost here.
Are your preparations going well?
Yes.
The whole class coming together
as one to achieve a common goal
has been a really great experience.
Oh, really?
I can't wait to see it.
Rebecca?
Lord Evan...
You walked my fiancée home?
I'm Ray White.
Evan Bernstein.
It's an honor to meet you.
The honor is mine.
Well, then, Mr. White.
I'll accompany her myself from here.
All right.
Then, excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Let's go, Rebecca.
There must be something to Evan Bernstein.
Sir?
There's no evidence of humans
living in the Bernstein manor.
No servants, let alone
members of the household.
It seems to have been completely
abandoned for several years.
But Evan Bernstein has been
attending aristocratic gatherings
and academic sorcery summits, right?
Correct.
It is likely that he has kept this
deception running for a long time,
as to avoid being found out by the
kingdom or the Sorcerer Society.
I see.
I'm starting to get it.
So he's after...
Rebecca Bradley's sorcerer's eyes.
That means...
Indeed.
It's most probable that Evan Bernstein
is a collector of sorcerer's eyes
and is involved with Eugenics.
So how was it?
We're almost there.
Once Rebecca Bradley awakens as Kreuz...
then the gate to Akasha will open.
Liese, I promise you will...
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
~ Next Episode Preview ~
This is the preview of the next episode of
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World!
The girl who sheds the tears of despair.
The turbulent skies that envelope everything
as if in concert with her heart.
The beautiful lily goes into bloom.
"The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest
Sorcerer Resonates With the Past"!
Episode 11
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Resonates with the Past
This has been your very own Lily White!